https://zcla.org/privacy-statement

Privacy StatementThank you for visiting the Zen Center of Los Angeles website. We value your trust and confidence in us, so we have provided this statement to give you full disclosure of what we do with your personal information when you place an order online.SecurityZCLA uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) when receiving and transmitting your personal information. This technology is the standard for encrypting sensitive information to prevent your data from being intercepted and read when being sent across the Internet.Name and AddressWe do not provide your name, billing address, shipping address, email address or any other personal information to anyone outside the Zen Center of Los Angeles. It will not be given to any third-party mailing lists. If you are receiving the e-Wheel or other electronic newsletters and no longer wish to, please email us at info @ zcla.org and we’ll remove your address from our mailing list.Credit Card InformationYour credit card number is not stored with your personal information. It is saved in a temporary record until your transaction has been processed, then deleted from our online database. The Zen Center of Los Angeles uses Authorize.net, the leading online transaction gateway, to process your credit card transaction, and the entire checkout process is secured with SSL.EventsFull CalendarUpcoming EventsMeditation Retreats2020 Rohatsu SesshinRetreat DescriptionsScheduled RetreatsRetreat FeesSesshin/Zazenkai Tenzo2020 Fall Practice PeriodNewcomersClasses for NewcomersIntro to Zen Meditation ClassExploring Your Zen PracticeHow to Sit ZazenAbout the Zendo (Meditation Hall)Layout & HistoryGuidelinesPrecautionsAltarTrainingOverviewClassesFall 2020 Precept Class2020 Jukai SeriesDay of ReflectionLiving at ZCLAGuest ProgramResidencyPositionsResourcesPhoto GalleryVideo GalleryArticlesNewsletter ArchiveAboutOur MissionZCLA FoundersAbbotTeachersStaffGovernanceShared StewardshipOrganizational StructureStewards of ZCLACore ValuesEthical GuidelinesStatement on RacismAffiliated Zen GroupsStoreDonationsShipping & ReturnsAccount InfoMembers AreaLogin/LogoutMember ResourcesRites of PassageRecorded TalksLibraryForms & PoliciesTextsPracticesSpecial ReportsLiturgyCalendarDaily ServicesSpecial CeremoniesGathas & VersesService PositionsMeal ServicesShared StewardshipService (Karma Sphere)Study (Vajra Sphere)Buddha SphereResources (Ratna Sphere)Relationships (Padma Sphere)Tenzo CircleCircle MinutesSupportDonateBecome a MemberFees & Member LevelsMembership ApplicationCook in the ZCLA KitchenPlanned GivingVolunteerContactGet in TouchDirectionsParkingName *FirstLastEmail *How did you find out about ZCLA?EmailSubmit  © 2020 Zen Center of Los Angeles. All Rights Reserved | Privacy StatementDonate0
